ninjaup.com 2011-06-24

# NinjaUp- Make Mass Mirror For Free - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Google Advertising Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the users based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Logging IP Addresses**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address. Our servers can detect the IP address of your browser according to Internet-technology. IP addresses are logged and used by ninjaup for measuring usage.

**Which data does ninjaup store about the files I upload?**

* IP address of the computer from which the upload is started
* Time of the upload
* The e-mail address entered by the uploader  

 **Collecting e-mail addresses**

We automatically collect the e-mail addresses entered by the uploader, but under no circumstances will ninjaup lease, sell, or provide your personal information to any companies. 

**Certain Exceptional Disclosures**

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process.

**Use of Cookies**

ninjaup may use cookies to store the preferences of users. However, we do not use any methods for tracking users (the so-called spy or gif images and so on). 

**File Transfer Security**

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. All files stored for delivery are deleted when they have been uploaded to third-party websites.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Your consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of these informations by ninjaup. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
